我已经接到了很多公司的邀请，毕竟，我会两种语言呢
I have had offers for many jobs.
我知道啊
Don't I know it.
还记得那个俄国贸易委员会吗？
Remember that Russian Trade Commission?
他们一天到晚给我打电话
They keep calling me all the time.
想要我想疯了
They want me very badly.
我敢打赌，那些个西伯利亚人都是老色鬼
I'll bet, those Siberian wolves.
所以你还是再找一个小蜜吧
So you better find yourself another girl.
好吧！
All right!
我说你写
Dictation.
刊登在柏林各大报纸的分类广告上
Classified ad to run in all Berlin papers.
引号里内容
Quote...
魅力无穷的中年经理
"Attractive middle aged executive...
特聘一位魅力无穷的年轻女秘书
"wants attractive, young secretary.
要求业务多面且有合作精神
"Must be versatile and cooperative.
薪水可观，工作条件舒适
"Excellent salary, congenial working conditions...